virtualbox.org 2019-12-31

# Privacy @ Oracle | Oracle

#### No results found

Your search did not match any results.

We suggest you try the following to help find what you're looking for:

  * Check the spelling of your keyword search.
  * Use synonyms for the keyword you typed, for example, try “application” instead of “software.”
  * Try one of the popular searches shown below.
  * Start a new search.

**Trending Questions**

Back

Oracle respects your preferences concerning the collection and use of your Personal Information. The following privacy policies are tailored for the different ways your Personal Information may be collected, used, shared and processed by different Oracle lines of business:

  * The Oracle General Privacy Policy addresses information we collect in connection with your use of our websites and mobile applications, your interactions with Oracle and in the context of our offline sales and marketing activities, including Profit Magazine and Oracle Magazine.
  * The Services Privacy Policy describes our privacy and security practices that apply when handling (i) _services personal information_ in order to perform Consulting, Technical Support, Cloud and other services on behalf of Oracle customers; and (ii) personal information contained in _systems operation data_ generated by the interaction of (end-)users of these services with Oracle systems and networks.
  * The Oracle Recruiting Privacy Policy addresses information we may collect in connection with Oracle's online and offline recruiting efforts.
  * The Oracle Data Cloud Privacy Policy addresses how Oracle facilitates the collection and use of marketing and interest-based information to help enable interest-based advertising by Oracle’s Marketing and Data Cloud customers.
  * The AddThis Privacy Policy informs consumers about the collection, use and sharing of personal information in connection with Oracle’s provision of the AddThis Tools and Toolbar.
  * The Dyn Internet Performance Tools Privacy Policy provides information on the collection, use, sharing and processing of personal information by Oracle in connection with Dyn’s Recursive DNS service, Updater Client, Gauge web browser extension, and RUM beacons.

If you would like to exercise your preferences or learn more about how you can control Oracle’s collection and use of your personal information, please refer to the ‘What are your Choices?’ section in each of these policies or to the Privacy Choices tab.
